[
  {
    "questionId": 1,
    "question": "3 (x + 1)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "4x + 3",
      "b": "4x + 4",
      "c": "3x + 3",
      "d": "3 + 1x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">3(x+1)<br/> = (3)(x+1)<br/> = (3)(x)<br/> = (3)(1)<br/> = 3x+3</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 2,
    "question": "4 (a + 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "a4 +  6",
      "b": "a4 + 8",
      "c": "4a + 6",
      "d": "4a + 8"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">4(a+2)<br/> = (4)(a+2)<br/> = (4)(a)<br/> = (4)(2)<br/> = 4a+8</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 3,
    "question": "5 (x + y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "5x + 5y",
      "b": "x5 + 5y",
      "c": "6 + 5y",
      "d": "6x + 5y"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">5(x  + y)<br/> = (5)(x+y)<br/> = (5)(x)<br/> = (5)(y)<br/> = 5x+5y</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 4,
    "question": "10 (a ‚Äì b)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "10a ‚Äì b ",
      "b": "a10 ‚Äì 10b",
      "c": "10a ‚Äì 10b",
      "d": "a10 ‚Äì 10b"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">10(a ‚Äì b)<br/> = (10)(a-b)<br/> = (10)(a)<br/> = (10)(-b)<br/> = 10a-10b<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 5,
    "question": "x (‚Äì2 + y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-x2 + xy",
      "b": "-2x + xy",
      "c": "x2 + xy",
      "d": "2x + xy"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">x(‚Äì2 + y)<br/> = (x)(-2+y)<br/> = (x)(-2)<br/> = (x)(y)<br/> = -2x+xy</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 6,
    "question": "‚Äì6 (5 ‚Äì y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-30 ‚Äì y6",
      "b": "-30 + 6y",
      "c": "30 + 6y",
      "d": "30 ‚Äì 6y"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">‚Äì6(5 ‚Äì y)<br/> = (-6)(5-y)<br/> = (-6)(5)<br/> = (-6)(-y)<br/> = -30+6y</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 7,
    "question": "2x (x + 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "2xx + 4x",
      "b": "xx2 + 4",
      "c": "3x + 4x",
      "d": "2x2 + 4x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">2x(x + 2)<br/> = (2x)(x+2)<br/> = (2x)(x)<br/> = (2x)(2)<br/> = 2x¬≤+4x<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 8,
    "question": "3x (x + 2y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "3x2 + 6xy",
      "b": "3x2 + 6yx",
      "c": "3x + 6xy",
      "d": "3x + 6yx"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">3x(x + 2y)<br/> = (3x)(x+2y)<br/> = (3x)(x)<br/> = (3x)(2y)<br/> = 3x¬≤+6xy</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 9,
    "question": "‚Äì2x (5x ‚Äì y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "10x2 ‚Äì 2xy",
      "b": "-10x + 2xy",
      "c": "-10x2 + 2xy",
      "d": "10x ‚Äì 2xy"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 10,
    "question": "5x (a + b)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "5ax + 5bx",
      "b": "5xa + 5bx",
      "c": "5xa + 5xb",
      "d": "5ax + 5 xb"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">5x (a + b)<br/> = (5x)(a + b)<br/> = (5x)(a) + (5x)(b)<br/> = 5ax + 5bx</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 11,
    "question": "3a (4x + 2y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "12ax + 6ay",
      "b": "12xa + 6ay ",
      "c": "12ax + 6ya ",
      "d": "12xa+ 6ya"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">3a (4x + 2y)<br/> = (3a)(4x) + (3a)(2y)<br/> = 12ax + 6ay</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 12,
    "question": "‚Äì4m (‚Äì2a ‚Äì 5b)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "8am+ 20bm",
      "b": "8ma + 20mb",
      "c": "8am + 20mb ",
      "d": "8ma + 20bm"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">‚Äì4m(‚Äì2a ‚Äì 5b)<br/> = (-4m)(-2a-5b)<br/> = (-4m)(-2a)<br/> = (-4m) (-5b)<br/> = 8ma + 20mb</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 13,
    "question": "2xy (a + xy)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "2axy+ 2x2y2",
      "b": "2xya+ 2y2x2",
      "c": "2xay+ 2x2y2",
      "d": "2xya+ 2x2y2"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">2xy(a + xy)<br/> = (2xy)(a + xy)<br/> = (2xy)(a)<br/> = (2xy)(xy)<br/> = 2xya + 2x2y2</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 14,
    "question": "3x2 (4x + 1)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "12x3 + 3x2",
      "b": "12x2 + 3x3",
      "c": "12x4 + 3x2",
      "d": "12x2 + 3x2"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">3x2(4x + 1)<br/> = (3x2)(4x + 1)<br/> = (3x2)(4x)<br/> = (3x2)(1)<br/> = 12x3 + 3x2</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 15,
    "question": "-7x2 (3x + 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "21x2 ‚Äì 14x2",
      "b": "-21x3 ‚Äì 14x2 ",
      "c": "-21x2 + 14x2",
      "d": "21x3 + 14x2"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">-7x2(3x + 2)<br/> = (-7x2) (3x + 2)<br/> = (-7x2) (3x) + (-7x2) (2)<br/> = -21x3  - 14x2</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 16,
    "question": "4x3 (2x ‚Äì 1) ",
    "choices": {
      "a": "8x4 ‚Äì 4x4",
      "b": "8x3 ‚Äì 4x3",
      "c": "8x3 ‚Äì 4x4",
      "d": "8x4 ‚Äì 4x3 "
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">4x3(2x ‚Äì 1)<br/> = (4x3)(2x - 1)<br/> = (4x3)(2x)= (4x3)(-1)<br/> = 8x4  - 4x3</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 17,
    "question": "x2y2 (2x + 3y)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "2x3y2 + 3x2y3",
      "b": "2x2y2 + 3x2y3",
      "c": "2 y2x3 + 3x2y3",
      "d": "2x3y2 + 3y3x2"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">x2y2(2x + 3y)<br/> = (x2y2) (2x + 3y)<br/> = (x2y2) (2x) + (x2y2) (3y)<br/> = 2x3 y2 + 3x2y3</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 18,
    "question": "-3x2y3 (7x ‚Äì 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-21x3y3 + 6x2 y3",
      "b": "-21x3y3 + 6y3x2",
      "c": "21 y3x3+ 6x2 y3",
      "d": "21x3y3 + 6x2y3 "
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">-3x2y3 (7x ‚Äì 2)<br/> = (-3x2y3)(7x ‚Äì 2)<br/> = (-3x2y3)(7x)<br/>= (-3x2y3)(-2)<br/> = -21x3 y3 + 6x2y3</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 19,
    "question": "5x3y6 (-2x2 + 4xy3)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-10y6x5 + 20x4y9",
      "b": "10x5y6 + 20 y9x4",
      "c": "10x5y6 + 20x4y9 ",
      "d": "-10x5y6 + 20x4y9"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">5x3y6(-2x2 + 4xy3)<br/> = (5x3y6)(-2x2 + 4xy3)<br/> = (5x3y6)(-2x2)<br/> = (5x3y6)(4xy3)<br/> = -10x5y6 + 20x4y9</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 20,
    "question": "-2x2y5 (‚Äì4x3y ‚Äì 7x2y3)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "8x5y6 + 14x4y8",
      "b": "-8x5y6 + 14x4y8",
      "c": "8x5y6 ‚Äì 14x4y8",
      "d": "-8x5y6 ‚Äì 14x4y8"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">-2x2y5(‚Äì4x3y ‚Äì 7x2y3)<br/> = (-2x2y5)(‚Äì4x3y) ‚Äì7x2y3)<br/> = (-2x2y5)(‚Äì4x3y)<br/> = (-2x2y5)(-7x2y3)<br/> = 8x5y6 + 14x4y8</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 21,
    "question": "2 (4 + 9w)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "6 + 18w",
      "b": "6 + w18",
      "c": "8 + 18w",
      "d": "8 + w18"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">2 (4 + 9w)<br/> = (2)(4 + 9w)<br/> = (2)(4)<br/> = (2)(9w)<br/> = 8 + 18w</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 22,
    "question": "-4 (-4d - 5)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-16d + 20",
      "b": "16d + 20",
      "c": "-16d ‚Äì 20",
      "d": "16d ‚Äì 20"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">-4 (-4d - 5)<br/> = (-4)(-4d - 5)<br/> = (-4)(-4d)<br/> = (-4)(-5)<br/> = 16d + 20</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 23,
    "question": "(2 - 5m)(-5)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-10 ‚Äì 25m",
      "b": "10 ‚Äì 25m",
      "c": "-10 + 25m",
      "d": "10 + 25m"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\"> (2 - 5m)(-5)<br/> = (2 - 5m)(-5)<br/> = (2)(-5)<br/> = (-5m)(-5)<br/> = -10 + 25m</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 24,
    "question": "2 (3v ‚Äì 8)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "5v ‚Äì 16",
      "b": "6v + 16",
      "c": "5v + 16",
      "d": "6v ‚Äì 16"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">2 (3v - 8)<br/> = (2)(3v - 8)<br/> = (2)(3v) = (2)(-8)<br/> = 6v ‚Äì 16</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 25,
    "question": "(‚àí4)(4 ‚àí 2ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-16 ‚Äì 8x",
      "b": "-16 + 8x",
      "c": "16 ‚Äì 8x",
      "d": "16 + 8x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí4)(4 ‚àí 2ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí4)(4 ‚àí 2ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí4)(4)<br/> = (‚àí4)(2ùë•)<br/> = -16 + 8x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 26,
    "question": "(2 - 5m)(-5)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-10 ‚Äì 25m",
      "b": "10 ‚Äì 25m",
      "c": "-10 + 25m",
      "d": "10 + 25m"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(2 - 5m)(-5)<br/> = (2 - 5m)(-5)<br/> = (2)(-5)<br/> = (-5m)(-5)<br/> = -10 + 25m<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 27,
    "question": "(‚àí6ùë• + 2)(‚àí1)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-6x ‚Äì 2",
      "b": "6x ‚Äì 2",
      "c": "-6x + 2",
      "d": "6x + 2"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí6ùë• + 2)(‚àí1)<br/> = (‚àí6ùë• + 2)(‚àí1)<br/> = (‚àí6ùë•)(-1)<br/> = ( 2)(‚àí1)<br/> = 6x ‚Äì 2</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 28,
    "question": "(‚àí5)(ùë• ‚àí 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "5x ‚Äì 10",
      "b": "5x + 10",
      "c": "-5x ‚Äì 10",
      "d": "-5x + 10"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí5)(ùë• ‚àí 2)<br/>  = (-5)(x + -2)<br/> = (-5)(x) + (-5)(-2)<br/>  = -5x + 10<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 29,
    "question": "2 (12 + 2ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "24 + x4",
      "b": "24 + 4x¬≤",
      "c": "24 + x4¬≤",
      "d": "24 + 4x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">2 (12 + 2ùë•)<br/> = (2)(12) + (2)(2ùë•)<br/> = 24 + 4x<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 30,
    "question": "(‚àí12ùë• + 14)(‚àí5)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "60x ‚Äì 70",
      "b": "-60x ‚Äì 70",
      "c": "-60x + 70",
      "d": "60x + 70"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(-12x + 14)(-5)<br/> = (-12x + 14)(-5)<br/> = (-12x)(-5) + (14)(-5)<br/> = 60x ‚Äì 70</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 31,
    "question": "(‚àí5)(4ùë• ‚àí 1) + 4 (ùë• + 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "16x + 13",
      "b": "16x ‚Äì13",
      "c": "-16x ‚Äì 13",
      "d": "-16x + 13"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí5)(4ùë• ‚àí 1) + 4 (ùë• + 2)<br/> = (‚àí5)(4ùë•) + (-5)(‚àí 1) + (4)(ùë•) + (4)(2)<br/> = -20x + 5 + 4x + 8<br/> = -20x + 5 + 4x + 8<br/> = (-20x + 4x) + (5 + 8)<br/> = -16x + 13</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 32,
    "question": "(‚àí3)(ùë• + 4) ‚àí (2 + 3ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "6x ‚Äì 14",
      "b": "-6x ‚Äì 14",
      "c": "6x + 14",
      "d": "-6x + 14"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí3)(ùë• + 4) ‚àí (2 + 3ùë•)<br/> = -3 (x+4) + (-1)(2+3x)<br/> = -3 (x+4) + (-1)(2)+ (-1)(3x)<br/> = -3 (x+4) + -2+ -3x<br/> = (-3)(x) + (-3)(4) + -2 + -3x<br/> = -3x + -12 + -2 + -3x<br/> = -3x + -12 + -2 + -3x<br/> = (-3x + -3x) + (-12 + -2)<br/> = -6x + -14<br/> = -6x ‚Äì 14</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 33,
    "question": "(10 ‚àí 2ùë•) 9",
    "choices": {
      "a": "90 + 18x",
      "b": "90 ‚Äì x18",
      "c": "90 + x18",
      "d": "90 ‚Äì 18x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(10 ‚àí 2ùë•) 9<br/> = (10)(9) + (-2ùë•)(9)<br/> = 90 ‚Äì 18x<br/> = -18x + 90<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 34,
    "question": "(1 ‚àí 9ùë•)(‚àí10)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "10 + 90x",
      "b": "-10 ‚Äì 90x",
      "c": "10 ‚Äì 90x",
      "d": "-10 + 90x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(1 ‚àí 9ùë•)(-10)<br/> = (1 ‚àí 9ùë•)(-10)<br/> = (1 )(-10)<br/> = ( -9ùë•)(-10)<br/> = -10 + 90x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 35,
    "question": "(‚àí5)(11ùë• ‚àí 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "55x + 10",
      "b": "-55x + 10",
      "c": "-55x ‚Äì10",
      "d": "55x ‚Äì10"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí5)(11ùë• ‚àí 2)<br/> = (‚àí5)(11ùë•) + (-5)(-2)<br/> = -55x + 10</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 36,
    "question": " (‚àí6)(ùë• + 8)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-6x ‚Äì 48",
      "b": "6x ‚Äì 48",
      "c": "6x + 48",
      "d": "-6x + 48"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí6)(ùë• + 8)<br/> = (‚àí6)(ùë• + 8)<br/> = (‚àí6)(ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí6)( 8)<br/> = -6x ‚Äì 48<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 37,
    "question": "(‚àí4 + 3ùë•)(‚àí8)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-32 ‚Äì 24x",
      "b": "32 ‚Äì 24x",
      "c": "-32 + 24x",
      "d": "32 + 24x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí4 + 3ùë•)(‚àí8)<br/> = (‚àí4 + 3ùë•)(‚àí8)<br/> = (‚àí4)(‚àí8)<br/> = (3ùë•)(‚àí8)<br/> = 32 ‚Äì 24x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 38,
    "question": "(‚àí5)(1 ‚àí 11ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-5 + 55x",
      "b": "5 + 55x",
      "c": "-5 ‚Äì 55x",
      "d": "5 ‚Äì 55x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí5)(1 ‚àí 11ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí5)(1 ‚àí 11ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí5)(1)<br/> = (‚àí5)(-11ùë•)<br/> = -5 + 55x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 39,
    "question": "11 (3ùë• ‚àí 12)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-33x ‚Äì 132",
      "b": "33x + 132",
      "c": "33x ‚Äì 132",
      "d": "33 ‚Äì 132"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">11(3ùë• ‚àí 12)<br/> = (11)(3ùë• ‚àí 12)<br/> = (11)(3ùë•)<br/> = (11)(-12)<br/> = 33x ‚Äì 132</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 40,
    "question": "(8 ‚àí 2ùë•) 9",
    "choices": {
      "a": "72 ‚Äì 18x",
      "b": "82 ‚Äì 18x",
      "c": "62 ‚Äì 18x",
      "d": "52 ‚Äì 18x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(8 ‚àí 2ùë•)9<br/> = (8 ‚àí 2ùë•) (9)<br/> = (8)(9)<br/> = (-2ùë•)(9)<br/> = 72 ‚Äì 18x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 41,
    "question": "5 (7 + 9ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "35 + 55x",
      "b": "35 + 65x",
      "c": "35 + 45x",
      "d": "35 + 75x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">5 (7 + 9ùë•)<br/> = (5)(7 + 9ùë•)<br/> = (5)(7)<br/> = (5)(9ùë•)<br/> = 35 + 45x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 42,
    "question": "11 (5ùë• + 2)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "55x + 22",
      "b": "55 ‚Äì 22x",
      "c": "55x + 22",
      "d": "55 ‚Äì 22"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">11(5ùë• + 2)<br/> = (11)(5ùë• + 2)<br/> = (11)(5ùë•)<br/> = (11)(2)<br/> = 55x + 22</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 43,
    "question": "(‚àí4ùë• + 6) 6",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-24x + 36",
      "b": "-24x ‚Äì 36",
      "c": "24x ‚Äì 36",
      "d": "-4x + 36"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí4ùë• + 6)6<br/> = (‚àí4ùë• + 6)(6)<br/> = (‚àí4ùë•)(6)<br/> = (6)(6)<br/> = -24x + 36</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 44,
    "question": " (‚àí4)(4 ‚àí 2ùë•)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-16 ‚Äì 8x",
      "b": "16 + 8x",
      "c": "-16 + 8x",
      "d": "16 ‚Äì 8x"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí4)(4 ‚àí 2ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí4) (4 ‚àí 2ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí4) (4)  ‚àí (-4) (2ùë•)<br/> =  -16 + 8x</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 45,
    "question": "(‚àí12)(2ùë• + 1)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "24x + 12",
      "b": "24x ‚Äì 12",
      "c": "-24x + 12",
      "d": "-24x ‚Äì 12"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(‚àí12)(2ùë• + 1)<br/> = (‚àí12)(2ùë• + 1)<br/> = (‚àí12)(2ùë•)<br/> = (‚àí12)(1)<br/> = -24x ‚Äì 12</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 46,
    "question": "(3b - 2)(-3)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-9b + 6",
      "b": "9b ‚Äì 6",
      "c": "-9b + 6",
      "d": "-b ‚Äì6"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(3b - 2)(-3)<br/> = (3b - 2)(-3)<br/> = (3b)(-3)<br/> = (-2)(-3)<br/> = -9b + 6</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 47,
    "question": "(7x - 8)(-1)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "7x + 8",
      "b": "-7x + 8",
      "c": "-7x ‚Äì 8",
      "d": "7x ‚Äì 8"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "180",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(7x - 8)(-1)<br/> = (7x - 8)(-1)<br/> = (7x)(-1)<br/> = (-8)(-1)</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 48,
    "question": "(-5f + 8) 4",
    "choices": {
      "a": "-20f + 36",
      "b": "20f + 32",
      "c": "20f + 36",
      "d": "-20f + 32"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "d",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">(-5f + 8)4<br/> = (-5f + 8)(4)<br/> = (-5f)(4)<br/> = (8)(4)<br/> = -20f + 32</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 49,
    "question": "8 (2 + 9v)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "16 + 62v",
      "b": "16 + 72v",
      "c": "16 + 82v",
      "d": "16 + 52v"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">8(2 + 9v)<br/> = (8)(2 + 9v)<br/> = (8)(2)<br/> = (8)(9v)<br/> = 16 + 72v</p>"
  },
  {
    "questionId": 50,
    "question": "-4 (9k + 9)",
    "choices": {
      "a": "36k + 36",
      "b": "-36k + 36",
      "c": "-36k ‚Äì 36",
      "d": "36k ‚Äì 36"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
	"points": "280",
	"solution": "<p class=\"text-h5 lh-solution\">-4(9k + 9)<br/> = (-4)(9k + 9)<br/> = (-4)(9k)<br/> = (-4)(9)<br/> = -36k - 36</p>"
  }
]